
export const baseStruct = [
    {
        question: "2x1=?",
        answers: [2, 0, 1, 3],
        correct: 2
    },
    {
        question: "2x2=?",
        answers: [2, 4, 6, 8],
        correct: 4
    },
    {
        question: "2x3=?",
        answers: [2, 4, 6, 8],
        correct: 6
    },
    {
        question: "2x4=?",
        answers: [2, 4, 6, 8],
        correct: 8
    },
    {
        question: "2x5=?",
        answers: [2, 14, 10, 8],
        correct: 10
    },
    {
        question: "2x6=?",
        answers: [12, 24, 16, 8],
        correct: 12
    },
    {
        question: "2x7=?",
        answers: [24, 20, 16, 14],
        correct: 14
    }, 
    {
        question: "2x8=?",
        answers: [14, 24, 16, 8],
        correct: 16
    }, 
    {
        question: "2x9=?",
        answers: [12, 22, 16, 18],
        correct: 18
    }, 
    {
        question: "2x10=?",
        answers: [20, 24, 10, 18],
        correct: 20
    },
]

